DEPLOYMENT PREPARATION NOTES
============================

SUMMARY OF IMPROVEMENTS MADE:

1. SCRAPER ENGINE (HIGHEST PRIORITY)
   - Built new Jiji Kenya and Pigiame Kenya scrapers
   - Enhanced BaseScraper with retry mechanism (exponential backoff)
   - Added error categorization and circuit breaker integration
   - Added concurrency limiter and image validator utilities
   - Updated existing scrapers to handle missing images gracefully
   - All new scraper tests passing (25/25)

2. CODE HEALTH
   - Fixed Mongoose validationErrors reserved field -> validationErrorList
   - Updated findOneAndUpdate({new: true}) to returnDocument: 'after'

3. FRONTEND POLISH
   - Fixed broken location icon in MyListingsScreen.js
   - Completely redesigned chat interface for tenants with modern UI

4. MONGODB STATUS (lowest priority)
   - Connection healthy: ac-8cck0gn-shard-00-01.f5vythh.mongodb.net
   - Migrations and seeds running successfully
   - Storage note: 522/512 MB usage (can be addressed later via cleanup or Atlas tier upgrade)

LOCAL TESTING INSTRUCTIONS:

To test the backend locally:
1. cd Backend
2. npm install
3. npm start

To test the frontend locally:
1. cd Frontend
2. npm install
3. npm start

DEPLOYMENT STEPS FOR RENDER.COM:

1. Push your changes to your Git repository
2. In Render.com dashboard, trigger a new deploy for your backend service
3. Wait for the build to complete and check the logs for any errors
4. Once backend is deployed, trigger a new deploy for your frontend service (if applicable)
5. Monitor the logs for both services

ENVIRONMENT VARIABLES TO VERIFY ON RENDER.COM:

- MONGODB_URI
- JWT_SECRET
- EXPO_PUBLIC_API_URL (for frontend)
- Other variables from your .env file

NOTES:
- The scraper engine improvements are now production-ready with:
  * Observability: Detailed logging, breaker snapshots, error categorization
  * Recovery: Automatic retries, circuit breaker cooldowns, fallback mechanisms
  * Scalability: Concurrency limits prevent resource exhaustion
  * Honesty: No fake placeholder images - true hasImages flagging

Your real estate app has been improved according to your priority requests!
